<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vine&#39;s Crafts on My Hugo Hinode Site</title>
    <link>https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vine&#39;s Crafts on My Hugo Hinode Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FLibGoLite</title>
      <link>https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/apps/flibgolite/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/apps/flibgolite/</guid>
      <description>FLibGoLite is easy to use lightweight home library server with OPDS catalog.&#xA;&amp;nbsp; The OPDS catalog format is a syndication format for electronic publications based on Atom and HTTP. OPDS catalogs enable the aggregation, distribution, discovery, and acquisition of electronic publications. (Wikipedia) FLibGoLite is multiplatform and can run on Windows, macOs and Linux. It uses SQLite database for book search index.&#xA;Current FLibGoLite release supports EPUB and FB2 (single files and zip archives) publications format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixyne</title>
      <link>https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/apps/pixyne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/apps/pixyne/</guid>
      <description>_&#xA;Pixyne is an application that allows you to quickly review your photo folders, safely delete bad and similar shots, fix the shooting dates, crop and ajust photos.&#xA;Pixyne application has a simple and intuitive interface:&#xA;With a click on photo you can mark to drop it in the trash. In Advanced mode you may also set or correct the EXIF shooting date crop the size and ajust selected photo. When you save changes, you can change all file names to EXIF shooting date format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BurnFix</title>
      <link>https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/apps/burnfix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://vinser.github.io/hugo-hinode/apps/burnfix/</guid>
      <description>Try to fix screen image retentions and burn in, look for screen defects&#xA;After turning off or moving the taskbar, you suddenly find that the logo in the corner of the screen and the search magnifier are still visible on your monitor or TV screen, although not as brightly.&#xA;This is the so-called image retention or burn-in.&#xA;This application can attempt to get rid of this effect on your LCD, LED or plasma screen by showing a special moving Signal Pattern for a period of time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
